[{"answer": "Oh, the beach", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What is it that isn't working", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Are you kidding? They can't cancel that show on me now, it's too late for me to book anything else for that weekend. Alright, alright ... okay, bye.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What's happening", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No thanks", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Where did you get those", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh yeah? How'd you do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You always break even", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What the hell was that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You know you could've thrown a pencil out the window and seen if that came back", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How're you doin' there, big guy?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What, have you got yourself a cold?", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "The reason I asked you in here, is I caught your appearance on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Anyway, the thinking here is that it would be best if you didn't do any more of these shows", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I am different, yeah", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Please", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Hi my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hi my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend, we have a problem", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, what is it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Kicked out?! Why?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "How're things going? You wanna know how things are going? I'll tell you how things are going. I am getting kicked out of my apartment", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know! They have a list of grievances", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah, the jewel thief", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Alright, let's go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm not gonna be nice. That's how I got the job", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Opposite. Cut to Monk'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opposite.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why'd you have to eat so many", "qsentId": 30}]